# Andrii Kotov

Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine



hakoda.ak@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mhakoda



https://www.mhakoda.com

## Summary

I'm currently working as a web developer in Altairlabs affiliate network. I also develop my own commercial iOS application Fastriver, a new tool for e-commerce in Ukraine, allowing merchants to keep records of their goods and orders and track their payment and delivery.

Previously, I was an entrepreneur and worked on some great projects, King Apdo, Say Me, Pleasant Space, and others. Developing and programming for the web and mobile devices has always been a pleasure for me. I was drawn into this industry by my brother, to whom I am very grateful for his support and help.

## **Experience**



## Web Developer

Altairlabs

Aug 2021 - Present (10 months +)



Sole Proprietor Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 (2 years)

#### **Education**



### Ivan Franko National University of Lviv

**Business/Managerial Economics** Sep 2015 - Jul 2018 Some University Courses

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Certificate of Completion - 100 Days of SwiftUI - Hacking with Swift

#### Skills

iOS Development • Swift • SwiftUI • Application Development • GitHub • Xcode • WebKit • Firebase